Guide to the Pittsburgh Irish and Classical Theatre Records, 1997-2015 CTC.2009.02
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Productions, 1997-2014; I.
  - 2005 Season, 9.
    - Heartbreak House, June 2005
      - Newspaper clippings, June 2005 (Box 11, Folder 1)
      - Photographs (Box 11, Folder 2)
      - Program (Box 11, Folder 3)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 11, Folder 4)
      - Video recording, 2 videos Digital video cassette master (Box 11, Folder 5)
      - Video recording, 2 discs DVD user copy (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Stones in his Pockets
      The play Stones in His Pockets was written by Marie Jones and directed by Stuart Carden. The rival ran from June 29-July 17, 2005, at the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Jay O'Berski and Joe Schulz.
      - Program (Box 11, Folder 7)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - The False Servant, 2005
      The False Servant was written by Pierre Marivaux, and newly translated by Martin Crimp. It was directed by Stuart Carden in a run from July 28-August 20, 2005, at the Henry Heymann Theatre. This was a U.S. Premiere. AEA members involved in the production include Kate Eastwood Norris, Ian Merrill Peakes, Joe Schulz, Robin Walsh, Alicia DeMara, and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings (Box 11, Folder 9)
      - Photographs (Box 11, Folder 10)
      - Program (Box 11, Folder 11)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Video recording, 1 video Digital video cassette master (Box 11, Folder 13)
      - Video recording, 1 video VHS user copy (Box 11, Folder 14)
      - Video recording, 1 disc DVD user copy (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Henry, August-September 2005
      The play Henry was written by Thomas Kilroy, after Pirandello. This world premiere production was directed by Andrew S. Paul in a run from August 31-September 24, 2005, at the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved in the performance include Richard McMillan, Joe Schulz, Martin Giles, Ben Hersey, Joel Ripka, Erin Krom, Robin Walsh, Larry John Meyers, Sam Tsoutsouvas, Alicia DeMara, and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, 2004-2005 (Box 11, Folder 16)
      - Photographs (Box 11, Folder 17)
      - Program (Box 11, Folder 18)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 11, Folder 19)
      - Video recording, 2 videos Digital video cassette master (Box 11, Folder 20)
      - Video recording, 3 discs DVD user copy (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - 2006 Season, 10.
    - The Pillowman, May 2006
      The Pillowman was written by Martin McDonagh, and directed by Stuart Carden, in a run from May 4-28, 2006, at the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members involved in this Pittsburgh premiere production include Alex Moggridge, Tom Atkins, Simon Bradbury, Jennifer Tober, Matt Gaydos, and Alicia DeMara. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, May 2006 (Box 12, Folder 1)
      - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - Program (Box 12, Folder 3)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - Video recording, 1 video Digital video cassette master (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - Video recording, 1 disc DVD user copy (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - School for Scandal, June 2006
      The School for Scandal was written by Richard Brinsley Sheridan and directed by Andrew S. Paul, in a run from June 8 - 24, 2006, in the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved include Martin Giles, David Crawford, Marni Penning, Brian Barefoot, Matt Gaydos, Sheila McKenna, Roger Jerome, Douglas Rees, Vanessa Mandeville Morosco, Kevin Lageman, Joel Ripka, Alicia DeMara, and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, June 2006 (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Program (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 12, Folder 10)
      - Video recording, June 21, 2006; 1 video Digital video cassette master (Box 12, Folder 11)
      - Video recording, June 21, 2006; 1 disc DVD user copy (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Boston Marriage, July 2006
      The play Boston Marriage was written by David Mamet. This Pittsburgh premiere production was directed by Jeffrey M. Cordell and performed at the Henry Heymann Theatre, June 6-29, 2006. AEA members appearing in the performance are Melanie Dreyer, Derdriu Ring, and Karen Baum,
      - Newspaper clippings, July 2006 (Box 12, Folder 13)
      - Program (Box 12, Folder 14)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Video recording, 1 video Digital video cassette master (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Video recording, 1 disc DVD user copy (Box 12, Folder 17)
    - BeckettFest, 2006
      The play Endgame was written by Samuel Beckett. This production was directed by Tadeusz Bradecki and performed during Beckettfest, which ran from August 17 - September 10 in the Charity Randall and Henry Heymann Theatres. AEA members in Endgame include Larry John Meyers, Simon Bradbury, E. Bruce Hill, and Kate Young. Beckett's Happy Days was performed on September 7, 2006. AEA members in that production were Martin Giles and Kate Young.
      - Newspaper clippings, 2006 (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 19)
      - Program (Box 12, Folder 20)
      - Promotional materials (Box 12, Folder 21)
      - Video recording - Endgame, 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 12, Folder 22)
      - Video recording - Happy Days, September 7, 2006; 1 disc DVD (Box 12, Folder 23)
    - The Shaughraun, December 2006
      The Shaughraun was written by Dion Boucicault and directed by Andrew S. Paul, in a run from December 6-23, 2006, at the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Diana Donnelly, Susan McGregor-Laine, David Whalen, Lisa Anne Goldsmith, Martin Giles, David Cabot, Jason McCune, Darren Eliker, Karen Baum, Simon Bradbury, Patricia Angelin, Alicia DeMara, and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, December 2006 (Box 12, Folder 24)
      - Photographs (Box 12, Folder 25)
      - Program (Box 12, Folder 26)
      - Promotional materials (Box 12, Folder 27)
      - Video recording, 1 video Digital video cassette master (Box 12, Folder 28)
      - Video recording, 1 disc DVD user copy (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - 2007 Season, 11.
    - Julius Caesar, April 2007
      William Shakespeare's Julius Caesar was performed from May 10 - June 2, 2007 at the Henry Heymann Theatre. It was directed by Andrew S. Paul. AEA members involved in the production include: Ken Bolden, Larry John Meyers, Martin Giles, Catherine Moore, David Whalen, Mark Thompson, Richard McMillan, Allen Gilmore, Alex Coleman, Joshua Elijah Reese, Paul Ford, and Jarrod DiGiorgi. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Education flyer (Box 13, Folder 1)
      - Newspaper clippings, April 2007 (Box 13, Folder 2)
      - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - Program (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Stuff Happens, 2007-2008
      The play Stuff Happens was written by David Hare and directed by Andrew S. Paul in a run from May 10 - June 2, 2007, performed at the Henry Heymann Theatre. It was a Pittsburgh premiere. AEA members involved in the production include Richard McMillan, Allen Gilmore, Larry John Meyers, Pascale Armand, Randy Kovitz, Doug Mertz, Robert Haley, David Whalen, Martin Giles, Laurie Klatscher, Robert Haley, David Crawford, Jarrod DiGiorgi, Phill Madore, and Kerri Lynch. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Newspaper clippings - Poland tour, 2008 (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Program (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Video recording, 2 videos Digital video cassette (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - The Empire Series, 2007
      There were three plays that comprised PICT's The Empire Series - Via Dolorosa, Nine Parts of Desire, and Finn performed by Mabou Mines. They were performed for short runs through April, May, and June 2008.
      - Newspaper clippings - Via Dolorosa, 2007 (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Photographs - Nine Parts of Desire (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 13, Folder 14)
    - Hedda Gabler, June 2007
      The play Hedda Gabler was written by Henrik Ibsen and adapted by Judith Thompson. It was directed by Tadeusz Bradecki in a run from June 14 - June 30, 2007, in the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members include Matin Giles, Robin Walsh, Ingrid Sonnichsen, John Shepard, Paul Todaro, Susan McGregor-Laine, Alicia DeMara, and Phill Madore.
      - Newspaper clippings, June 2007 (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Program (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 13, Folder 18)
      - Video recording, 1 video Digital video cassette master (Box 13, Folder 19)
      - Video recording, 1 disc DVD user copy (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - The Lieutenant of Inishmore, July 2007
      The Lieutenant of Inishmore was written by Martin McDonagh and directed by Stuart Carden. This Pittsburgh premiere ran from July 12 - August 4, 2007, in the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members include Matt DeCaro, David Whalen, Jason McCune, Philip Winters, Jarrod DiGiorgi, Alicia DeMara and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, July 2007 (Box 13, Folder 21)
      - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 22)
      - Program (Box 13, Folder 23)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - Video recording, 1 video Digital video cassette master (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - Video recording, 1 disc DVD user copy (Box 13, Folder 26)
    - Private Lives, August 2007
      The play Private Lives was written by Noel Coward and directed by Jeffrey M. Cordell, in a run from August 16 - September 9, 2007, at the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members involved in the performance include Winslow Corbett, Paul Todaro, Ross Hellwig, Beth Hylton, and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, August 2007 (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - Photographs (Box 13, Folder 28)
      - Program (Box 13, Folder 29)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 13, Folder 30)
      - Video recording, 1 video Digital video cassette master (Box 13, Folder 31)
      - Video recording, 1 disc DVD user copy (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Pride and Prejudice, December 2007
      The play Pride & Prejudice was written by Jon Jory, and based on the novel of the same name by Jane Austen, was directed and choreographed by Scott Wise, in a run from December 6 - 22, 2007, at the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved include Leah Curney, David Whalen, Dixie Tymitz, Philip Winters, Theo Allyn, James FitzGerald, Joel Ripka, Lisa Ann Goldsmith, Michael Fuller, Linda Kimbrough, Phill Madore, and Ashley J. Martin. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Education flyer (Box 14, Folder 1)
      - Newspaper clippings, December 2007 (Box 14, Folder 2)
      - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 3)
      - Program (Box 14, Folder 4)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 14, Folder 5)
      - Video recording, December 22, 2007; 2 videos Digital video cassette master (Box 14, Folder 6)
      - Video recording, December 22, 2007; 2 discs DVD user copy (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - 2008 Season, 12.
    - King Lear, 2007-2008
      The play King Lear was written by William Shakespeare, and directed by James J. Christy, in a run from April 9-26, 2008, at the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Dakin Matthews, Larry John Meyers, David Whalen, Paul Todaro, Matt DeCaro, Simon Bradbury, Dereck Walton, Helena Ruoti, Robin Walsh, Karen Baum, Mark D. Staley, David Cabot, Randy Kovitz, Jarrod DiGiorgi, Alicia DeMara, and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Audience feedback, April 16, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 8)
      - Education flyer (Box 14, Folder 9)
      - Newspaper clippings, April 2008 (Box 14, Folder 10)
      - Performance reports, April 2008 (Box 14, Folder 11)
      - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 12)
      - Production meeting reports, 2007-2008 (Box 14, Folder 13)
      - Program (Box 14, Folder 14)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Rehearsal reports, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 16)
      - Set designs and prop photos, 2008 (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - Video recording, April 25, 2008; 2 videos Digital video cassette (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - An Ideal Husband, May 2008
      The play An Ideal Husband was written by Oscar Wilde and directed by Andrew S. Paul in a run from May 8 -31, 2008, in the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Paul Todaro, David Whalen, Beth Hylton, Nike Doukas, James FitzGerald, Kathleen Huber, Catherine Moore, Mary Rawson, E. Bruce Hill, Ashley J. Martin, and Niki Armato. Photographs by Erick Leininger.
      - Newspaper clippings, May 2008 (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Photographs (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Program (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Video recording, 2 videos Digital video cassette (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Wilde Tales, 2008
      The musical Wilde Tales was written by Bruce Dow, and based on Oscar Wilde's stories The Happy Prince and The Selfish Giant. This world premiere production was directed by Sheila McKenna, in a run from May 22-31, 2008, at the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved in the performance include David Cabot, Joshua Desjardins, Kelsey Robinson, and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, 2008 (Box 15, Folder 1)
      - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 2)
      - Program (Box 15, Folder 3)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - Video recording, 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Salome, June 2008
      The play Salome was written by Oscar Wilde and directed by Alan Stanford in a run from June 12-28, 2008, at the Charity Randall Theatre. Original music was composed and performed by Roger Doyle. AEA members involved in the production include Nicole Underhay, Jim Mezon, David Whalen, Kate Young, Doug Pona, Paul Todaro, Jarrod DiGiorgi, Catherine Moore, Jennifer Tober, James FitzGerald, Niki Armato, and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, June 2008 (Box 15, Folder 6)
      - Photographs (Box 15, Folder 7)
      - Program (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - Video recording, 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Synge Cycle, 2008
      The Synge Cycle was performed during a centenary celebration of John Millington Synge. The Playboy of the Western World, directed by Andrew S. Paul, along with the one-act plays When the Moon Has Set, Dierdre of the Sorrows, Riders to the Sea, The Well of the Saints, The Tinker's Wedding, The Shadow of the Glen comprised the cycle. The plays ran from July 17 - August 17, 2008 in the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved in the productions include Bridget Connors, Jon Farris, Martin Giles, Jerzy Gwiazdowski, Mari Howells, Susan McGregor-Laine, Phill Madore, Jason McCune, Kevin Murphy, Derdriu Ring, Philip Winters, and Kate Young. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 1)
      - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 2)
      - Program (Box 16, Folder 3)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 16, Folder 4)
      - Video recording, 4 videos Digital video cassette (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Elaine Stritch at Liberty, 2008
      Elaine Stritch at Liberty was presented by the Pittsburgh Irish & Classical Theatre in association with Cabaret Pittsburgh. The performance was October 18, 2008 at the Charity Randall Theatre.
      - Newspaper clippings, 2008 (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Dublin Carol / St. Nicholas, December 2008
      The play Dublin Carol was written by Conor McPherson and directed by Jackie Maxwell, in a run from December 4-20, 2008, at the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include: Larry John Meyers, Colleen Madden, and Phill Madore. Also being performed each night was another McPherson play, St. Nicholas. It was also directed by Andrew S. Paul and AEA members Martin Giles and Phill Madore were involved in the production. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, December 2008 (Box 16, Folder 8)
      - Photographs - Dublin Carol (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - Program (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 16, Folder 11)
      - Video recording - Dublin Carol, December 12, 2008; 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 16, Folder 12)
  - 2009 Season, 13.
    - Rock 'n' Roll, 2009
      The play Rock 'n' Roll was written by Tom Stoppard and directed by Andrew S. Paul, in a run from May 7-30, 2009, at the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Sam Redford, Sam Tsoutsouvas, Helena Ruoti, Simon Bradbury, Jarrod DiGiorgi, Martin Giles, Tami Dixon, Phill Madore, and Niki Armato. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Newspaper clippings, 2009 (Box 16, Folder 13)
      - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 14)
      - Program (Box 16, Folder 15)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 16, Folder 16)
      - Video recording, May 29, 2009; 2 videos Digital video cassette (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - What the Butler Saw, June 2009
      The play What the Butler Saw was written by Joe Orton and directed by Simon Bradbury in a run from June 11-27, 2009, at the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Douglas Rees, Helena Ruoti, Martin Giles, Jeffrey Carpenter, and Phill Madore. Photographs by Suellen Fitzsimmons.
      - Photographs (Box 16, Folder 18)
      - Program (Box 16, Folder 19)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 16, Folder 20)
      - Video recording, June 17, 2009; 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Doubt, July 2009
      The play Doubt was written by John Patrick Shanley and directed by Jeffrey M. Cordell in a run from July 9 - August 1, 2009, at the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members include David Whalen, Kate Young, Meghan Heimbecker, Maria Becoates-Bey, and Niki Armato.
      - Program (Box 17, Folder 1)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 17, Folder 2)
      - Video recording, July 24, 2009; 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - The History Boys, August 2009
      The History Boys was written by Alan Bennett and directed by Andrew S. Paul, in a run from August 6-22, 2009, at the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Dave Droxler, Andy Lutz, Jarid Faubel, Eric Berryman, Sam Redford, Bernard Cuffling, Martin Giles, Linda Kimbrough, James FitzGerald, Phill Madore, and Cory F. Goddard.
      - Program (Box 17, Folder 4)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 17, Folder 5)
      - Video recording, August 15, 2009; 2 videos Digital video cassette (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Crime & Punishment, September 2009
      Crime and Punishment was written by Fyodor Dostoevsky, and adapted for the stage by Marilyn Campbell and Curt Columbus. It was directed by Matthew Gray, in a run from September 10 - October 3, 2009, in the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Joel Ripka, Larry John Meyers, Susan Goodwillie, and Niki Armato.
      - Promotional postcard (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - Video recording, September 30, 2009; 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Jane Eyre
      The play Jane Eyre was written by Alan Stanford and adapted from the novel by Charlotte Bronte. It was directed by Scott Wise and composed by Douglas Levine, in a run from December 3-20, 2009, at the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved in the performance include Shelley Delaney, Catherine Moore, Larry John Meyers, Allison McLemore, Kate Young, David Whalen, Anna Van Valin, Joel Ripka, James FitzGerald, Lisa Ann Goldsmith, Phill Madore, and Cory F. Goddard.
      - Program (Box 17, Folder 9)
      - Promotional postcard (Box 17, Folder 10)
      - Video recording, 2 videos Digital video cassette (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - 2010 Season, 14.
    - Beautiful Dreamers, April 2010
      The musical Beautiful Dreamers was written and directed by Martin Giles, with arrangements and musical direction by Douglas Levine. It featured the songs of Stephen Foster and ran April 15-May 1, 2010, in the Charity Randall Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Joel Ripka, Stephanie Riso, Michael Fuller, Daniel Krell, Daina Michelle Griffith, and Phill Madore.
      - Program (Box 17, Folder 12)
      - Video recording, April 30, 2010; 2 videos Digital video cassette (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Othello, May 2010
      The play Othello was written by William Shakespeare and directed by Andrew S. Paul, in a run from May 20 - June 12, 2010, in the Henry Heymann Theatre. AEA members involved in the production include Javon Johnson, Michael Hanrahan, Larry John Meyers, Jay Stratton, Joel Ripka, Martin Giles, Daryll Heysham, Allison McLemore, Shelley Delaney, Cory F. Goddard, and Phill Madore.
      - Program (Box 18, Folder 1)
      - Video recording, May 28, 2010; 2 videos Digital video cassette (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Hearing Noise in the Silence: A Pinter Celebration, August 2010
      Hearing Noise in the Silence: A Pinter Celebration was comprised of six Harold Pinter plays. The Hothouse, directed by Matthew Grey, No Man's Land, directed by Andrew S. Paul, along with the one-act plays The Dumb Waiter, Betrayal, The Room, and Celebration were performed in July and August, 2010 at the Charity Randall and Henry Heymann theatres. AEA members involved in the productions include Jarrod DiGiorgi, Tami Dixon, Nick Doukas, Martin Giles, Michael Hanrahan, Leo Marks, Rick McMillan, Larry John Meyers, Doug Pona, Bernadette Quigley, Sam Tsoutsouvas, and David Whalen.
      - Program (Box 18, Folder 3)
      - Video recording - Betrayal, August 15, 2010; 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 18, Folder 4)
        The play The Dumb Waiter was written by Harold Pinter and directed by Martin Giles. It was performed as part of the Pinter Celebration which ran from July 22 -August 22, 2010 in the Charity Randall and Henry Heymann Theatres. AEA members involved in the production include: Michael Hanrahan and Jarrod DiGiorgi. The play Betrayal was written by Harold Pinter and directed by Alan Stanford. It was performed as part of the Pinter Celebration which ran from July 22 -August 22, 2010 in the Charity Randall and Henry Heymann Theatres. AEA members involved in the production include: Nike Doukas, David Whalen, Leo Marks, and Martin Giles.
      - Video recording - Celebration & The Room, August 15, 2010; 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 18, Folder 5)
        The play Celebration was written by Harold Pinter and directed by Alan Stanford. It was performed as part of the Pinter Celebration which ran from July 22 -August 22, 2010 in the Charity Randall and Henry Heymann Theatres. AEA members involved in the production include: Michael Hanrahan, Nike Doukas, Martin Giles, Bernadetter Quigley, Leo Marks, Tami Dixon, and Rick McMIllan. The play The Room was written by Harold Pinter and directed by Shelia McKenna. It was performed as part of the Pinter Celebration which ran from July 22 -August 22, 2010 in the Charity Randall and Henry Heymann Theatres. AEA members involved in the production include: Martin Giles, Bernadette Quigley, Larry John Meyers, Fredi Bernstein, Jarrod DiGiorgi, and Doug Pona.
      - Video recording - No Man's Land, August 17, 2010; 1 video Digital video cassette (Box 18, Folder 6)